Fear reaches new heights.
Fall is a thriller film directed by Scott Mann.
For best friends Becky and Hunter, life is all about
conquering fears and pushing limits.
But after they climb 2,000 feet to the top of a remote, abandoned radio
tower, they find themselves stranded with no way down.
Now Becky and Hunter's expert climbing skills will be put to the ultimate test as they desperately
fight to survive the elements, a lack of supplies, and vertigo-inducing heights.
Becky Connor, played by Grace Caroline Currey.
Shiloh Hunter, played by Virginia Gardner.
James Conner, played by Jeffrey Dean Morgan.
Dan Connor, played by Mason Gooding.
Steve, played by Jasper Cole.
Randy, played by Darrell Dennis.
Fall is a 2022 survival psychological thriller film directed by
Scott Mann and written by Mann and Jonathan Frank.
Starring Grace Caroline Currey, Virginia Gardner, Mason Gooding and Jeffrey Dean Morgan, the film follows two women
who climb a 2,000-foot-tall (610 m) television broadcasting tower, before becoming stranded at the top.
It was theatrically released in the United States on
August 12, 2022 by Lionsgate Films.
The film was a box office success, grossing $21 million worldwide against a $3 million budget, and received generally positive reviews from
critics; Currey's and Gardner's performances were particularly praised, with criticism for the film's visual effects and screenplay.
The film explores themes of hallucination, stranded,
tower, free climbing, sport climbing.
The tone is intense.